var title = "The Alphabet";

// using array so that questions come in the right order
var questions = [

  {
    prompt: "Α α",
    answer: ["άλφα"],
    partial: ["αλφα"],
  },

  {
    prompt: "Β β",
    answer: ["βήτα"],
    partial: ["βητα"],
  },

  {
    prompt: "Γ γ",
    answer: ["γάμα"],
    partial: ["γαμα"],
  },

  {
    prompt: "Δ δ",
    answer: ["δέλτα"],
    partial: ["δελτα"],
  },

  {
    prompt: "Ε ε",
    answer: ["έψιλον"],
    partial: ["εψιλον"],
  },

  {
    prompt: "Ζ ζ",
    answer: ["ζήτα"],
    partial: ["ζητα"],
  },

  {
    prompt: "Η η",
    answer: ["ήτα"],
    partial: ["ητα"],
  },

  {
    prompt: "Θ θ",
    answer: ["θήτα"],
    partial: ["θητα"],
  },

  {
    prompt: "Ι ι",
    answer: ["γιώτα"],
    partial: ["ιωτα", "γιωτα"],
  },

  {
    prompt: "Κ κ",
    answer: ["κάπα"],
    partial: ["καπα"],
  },

  {
    prompt: "Λ λ",
    answer: ["λάμδα"],
    partial: ["λαμδα"],
  },

  {
    prompt: "Μ μ",
    answer: ["μι"],
    partial: [],
  },

  {
    prompt: "Ν ν",
    answer: ["νι"],
    partial: [],
  },

  {
    prompt: "Ξ ξ",
    answer: ["ξι"],
    partial: [],
  },

  {
    prompt: "Ο ο",
    answer: ["όμικρον"],
    partial: ["ομικρον"],
  },

  {
    prompt: "Π π",
    answer: ["πι"],
    partial: [],
  },

  {
    prompt: "Ρ ρ",
    answer: ["ρο"],
    partial: [],
  },

  {
    prompt: "Σ σ/ς",
    answer: ["σίγμα"],
    partial: ["σιγμα"],
  },

  {
    prompt: "Τ τ",
    answer: ["ταυ"],
    partial: [],
  },

  {
    prompt: "Υ υ",
    answer: ["ύψιλον"],
    partial: ["υψιλον"],
  },

  {
    prompt: "Φ φ",
    answer: ["φι"],
    partial: [],
  },

  {
    prompt: "Χ χ",
    answer: ["χι"],
    partial: [],
  },

  {
    prompt: "Ψ ψ",
    answer: ["ψι"],
    partial: [],
  },

  {
    prompt: "Ω ω",
    answer: ["ωμέγα"],
    partial: ["ωμεγα", "ώμεγα"],
  },
];
  
